What's this?
这是什么
I will pay top dollar for real photos of aliens and UFOs.
我愿意出高价卖真外星人或者真UFO的照片
Cool, now that's an assignment I would might having.
真棒   这就是我会做的工作
But where am I gonna see an UFO? It's not like they just pass by out of nowhere.
但我从哪里拍到UFO呢 他们又不会凭空飞出来
I'll take that back, there's one now. Slow down, I come in peace.
现成的就有一个   我要把那带回去 别飞那么快   我是为和平而来的
Must catch ya~
一定要抓到你
Yes, I gotch ya.
我抓到你啦
but it's smaller than I expected.
但是   怎么比想象中的要小
Hey, paws off my stuff !!!!
嘿   把你的脏手拿开
Oh, hey, Sneach! Big G!
噢   嘿   小夫   胖虎
Let go of it , you can't afford it.
把手放开   弄坏了你可赔不起
Oh, so it's just a toy.
唉   原来这只是个玩具
-Don't tell me you actually thought it was a real UFO?-Eh... no
-别告诉我 你真的以为这是个真UFO -额   当然没有